

Profile

I am an open-minded and multicultural sales professional with two years of experience, during which I contributed to sales expansion and sharpened my negotiation skills and adaptability. I have proven to be motivated by challenges, results, and customer satisfaction. I am ready to join an organization where I can fully express my potential.

Professional Experience (Internship)

May 2023 - November 2023 (7 months)

Maison Margiela | Paris, France: Retail Sales

- Managed client portfolio: Harrods, Le Bon Marché, Kith, Printemps...
- Sales administration with results tracking
- SEM benchmarking, preparing client folders during the launch campaigns of the new collection
- Prospecting and trend monitoring, benchmarking, and monitoring recommended retail prices (RRP).
- Preparation of monthly sales reports

March 2022 - August 2022 (6 months)

INFIA S.R.L. | Valencia, Spain: Supply Chain Coordinator

- Led the annual inventory with an analysis of product expiration dates
- Managed orders and organized their loading from Italy
- Managed returns with administrative handling

April 2021 - August 2021 (5 months)

Partida I Algésiras, Spain: Freight Forwarding Assistant

- Verified and prepared all necessary documents for smooth customs clearance operations
- Informed clients and carriers on the progress of these operations

January 2020 - March 2020 (3 months)

Maroc Fruit Board | Casablanca, Morocco: Logistics Coordinator

- Followed client shipments to North America and Russia
- Updated the Fresh Track platform on available transportation means to these destinations

May 2019 - August 2019 (3 months)

Mehadrin Tnuport Export | Rungis, France: International Sales Assistant

- Sales' administration
- Organized imports from Peru to European countries
- Conducted market research on the evolution of new retailers specializing in fresh products (Grand Frais and its competitors)

Education:

Master II in International Business

KEDGE Business School | France 2022 – 2024

Bachelor (BBA) in International Business

Toulouse Business School | Morocco, Spain, and exchange program in Japan 2019 – 2022

Architecture Preparatory Classes

École d'architecture Paris Val-de-Seine 2016 – 2018

Languages

- French Fluent
- English Fluent
- Arabic
- Spanish

Skills

- Prospecting and Negotiation
- B2B Sales
- Client Portfolio Management
- Customer Retention
- Key Account Management
- local and export sales
- Customer Needs Analysis
- Market Research
- Technical ERP tools

Interests

- Drawing, Sports, Traveling
- Coaching
- Member of the Sanady Foundation for combating school failure in Morocco
- Member of the Jood Association for the reintegration of the homeless

Personal Qualities

- Leadership
- Results-Oriented
- Team Spirit
- Autonomy
- Proactivity
- Adaptability and Perseverance